babelgum.com 2012-11-04

# Privacy Policy | Babelgum

**We, Babel Networks Limited, take the privacy rights of users of this Site and the Babelgum Services very seriously and this Privacy Policy explains to you what information we collect about you in connection with your use of the Site and Babelgum Services and how certain information about you may be used, stored and processed.**

**This Privacy Policy is incorporated in and subject to the**[ **Terms of Service**](http://www.babelgum.com/terms-of-service) **("Terms"). By using the Site and the Babelgum Services, you expressly consent to the use of your Data in accordance with this Privacy Policy.**

The Site is not intended for children under 13 years of age and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under this age.

**The definitions in the Terms shall apply to this Privacy Policy.**

**1\. Your Data**

"Your Data" means:

1.     any information about you which is personally identifiable, including, without limitation, your name, date of birth, gender, email address, address, country of residence, user name, password and other information from which you can be identified and which you may disclose to us or otherwise via the Site at any time.

2.     if you consent to “allow access” to your social networks accounts we will also collect and store basic account data and personal data provided from such social network accounts following your consent and this information may include data about your interests, friends, relationships and connections.

**2\. Collection of your Data**

We collect your Data when:

1.     you register with the Site;

2.     you make a complaint or enquiry or provide other feedback to us;

3.     you submit an entry to a questionnaire or survey, competition or prize draw; 

4.     you disclose your Data to us or otherwise through the Site at any other point;or

5.     you visit the Site having provided your consent to “allow access” to a social network site.

**3\. Use of your Data**

We use your Data to:

1.     process the registration of your online account and maintain your online account;

2.     process and deal with any complaints or enquiries made by you;

3.     monitor, develop and improve the Site, the Babelgum Services and your experience, and tailor the Site and the Babelgum Services to your specific preferences;

4.     investigate any suspected breach of the Terms made by or otherwise relating to you;

5.     where (and only where) agreed by you, to send you and keep you updated with information by email and/or SMS about existing and new services and special offers from us;

6.     where you have submitted an entry to a survey or questionnaire, to publish the results of such survey or questionnaire; and

7.     where you are a prize winner, to publish or otherwise make available a list of prize winners.

8.     To opt-out of receiving any information pursuant to paragraph 3.5 you can:

1.     amend your preferences accordingly in your on-line account;

2.     use the facility contained in any such communication; or

3.     email us at [support@babelgum.com](mailto:support@babelgum.com)

 9\. help us provide you with a more personalised service, we may record information about your usage of the Site, such as the channels, groups and favourites to which you subscribe, with which other users you share content, the videos you watch, information you display about yourself, as well as information you click on in the Site including user controls  and we may associate that information with your online account.

**4\. Passing on your Data to Third Parties**

1.     We may pass on your Data to other parties as follows:

1.     to our employees and agents to administer your on-line account and orders (including, without limitation, providing customer and marketing services, data analysis and postal and email delivery services);

2.     to Babel Networks Limited group companies to provide the Babelgum Services to you or to promote the services offered by us or them which may interest you;

3.     some general statistical information about the Site user base, sales patterns, traffic volumes and related matters may be passed on to reputable third parties but these details will not include information personally identifying you; or

4.     we may disclose your Data, without your consent, to the police, regulatory bodies or legal advisers in connection with any alleged criminal offence or suspected breach of the Terms by you or where required by law.

2.     By submitting a Notification through our [Copyright Notice](http://www.babelgum.com/copyright-policy) procedure, you agree that such communication can be forwarded to the person or entity who stored or transmitted the content addressed by your communication, in order to help resolve your complaint.

3.     From time to time, we may ask you to participate in surveys designed to help us improve the Site. Any Data provided to us in connection with any survey will be used only in relation to that survey, and will only be disclosed to third parties in non-personally-identifying form.

4.     We reserve the right to transfer all Data in our possession to a successor organization in the event of a merger, acquisition, or bankruptcy or other sale of all or a portion of  our assets. Other than to the extent ordered by a bankruptcy or other court, the use and disclosure of all transferred personally–identifying information will be subject to this Privacy Policy, or to a new privacy policy if you are given notice of that new privacy policy and are given an opportunity to affirmatively opt-in to accept it. Data submitted or collected after a transfer, however, may be subject to a new privacy policy adopted by the successor organization.

5.     The third parties to whom we pass on your Data will be restricted by law or under the terms of our confidentiality agreements with such third parties from using your Data for purposes other than those set out in this paragraph 4.

6.     We do not pass or sell your Data to third persons for any other purpose than those set out in this paragraph 4. Any marketing under paragraph3 is conducted by us on behalf of third parties and they do not have any access to your Data unless you yourself choose to contact them.

**5\. Data Security**

1.     We endeavour to take all reasonable steps to protect your Data. All the Data collected by us is stored on a secure server. The secure server software encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us.

2.     We recommend that you protect your password, username and your computer from access by unauthorised users. We suggest that you change your password on a regular basis. Please ensure that you sign out when you finish using the Babelgum Services.

3.     If you are resident in the United States we will notify you at the most current email address that you have provided to us in the event of a security breach. It is therefore extremely important that you update us if you change email addresses and that you make sure that we always have the most current email address for you on file. Any security breach notice will be sent to you as soon as possible following our discovery or notice of a security breach, and without unreasonable delay, subject to any determination by a law enforcement agency that notice would impede a criminal investigation, in which case the notice will be sent once the agency determines that notice will not compromise the investigation. If you would prefer to receive a security breach notice by regular mail, advise us of that fact by writing to us at: Floor 9, 665 Fifth Avenue, New York City, NY 10022, USA.

4.     Unfortunately and notwithstanding paragraphs 5.1 to 5.3 above, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your Data, we cannot guarantee the security of your Data transmitted to the Site; any transmission is at your own risk.

**6\. Cookies**

1\. Cookies are small pieces of information stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to allow us to understand who has seen which pages and advertisements and when, to determine how frequently particular pages are visited, to determine the most popular areas of the Site and most popular Content and generally in order to monitor usage of the Site. We also use cookies to enable us to customise your experience of the Babelgum Services and to target Content and advertising in accordance with your preferences. 

2.     Some advertisements on our Site are provided by third parties. Our advertising partners may serve ads that they believe are most likely to be of interest to you, based on information about your visit to this and other websites (this information is anonymous in that it does not include your name, street address, e-mail address or telephone number). In order to do this, our advertising partners may need to place a cookie on your computer. 

3.    Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, though you do not have to. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties. If you wish to disable cookies then you can do so by readjusting your browser settings although please note that by disabling cookies you may not be able to register with or use all features of the Site. For more information about this type of online behavioural advertising, about cookies, and about how to turn this feature off, you can consult the information provided by the Interactive Advertising Bureau at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). and [www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/). 

4.     A " **Web Beacon** " is an object that is embedded in a web page that is usually invisible to the user and allows website operators to check whether a user has viewed a particular web page. We (or third parties authorised to act on our behalf) may use Web Beacons on the Site to count users who have visited particular pages and to deliver co-branded services. Web Beacons are not used to access users' Data; they are a technique we may use to compile aggregated statistics about Site usage. Web Beacons collect only a limited set of information including a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the Web Beacon resides. You may not decline Web Beacons, however, they can be rendered ineffective by declining all cookies or modifying your browser setting to notify you each time a cookie is tendered and permit you to accept or decline cookies on an individual basis.

**7\. Access to and Updating your Data**

1.     Where you are a registered online account holder, you may access and update your Data contained in your online account by accessing the "Settings" section of the Site. You must make sure that you update your Data as soon as possible with any and all relevant changes. You may also delete your registered online account and your Data from our system. Please note that you will not be able to access certain of the Babelgum Services if you delete your Data.

2.     If you would like to receive a copy of your Data held by us, please email us at [support@babelgum.com](mailto:support@babelgum.com) we may charge you a small administration fee to comply with your request.

**8\. Location of your data**

We hold your Data in Ireland where the Site servers are located. As set out in paragraph 4, we may pass onto Babel Networks Limited group companies or reputable third parties general statistical information about the Site user base, sales patterns, traffic volumes and related matters but these details will not include information personally identifying you. In addition, we may need to share your information (including in some instances personally identifying information) with reputable third parties for the purposes described in paragraph 4.1.1 above. These Babel Networks Limited group companies or reputable third parties may be based outside the EEA and, by using the Site and the Babelgum Services, you expressly agree that we may transfer your Data outside the EEA solely for these purposes.

**9\. Other links**

Please be aware that the Site may link to other web sites that may be accessed by you through our Site. We are not responsible for the data policies, content or security of these linked web sites. We do not have any control over the use to which third parties may put your Data where you choose to purchase products or services or otherwise to contact them via this Site. It is your responsibility to review the data policies, content or security of these linked websites.

**10\. Changes to this privacy policy**

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time by giving you notice or by publishing the modified Privacy Policy on the Site. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy (as amended by us from time to time). However, we will not use your Data for any new purposes without your consent. If any amendment to this Privacy Policy is unacceptable to you, you should cease using the Site and/or the Babelgum Services. If you continue using the Babelgum Services following notification of the modified Privacy Policy, you will be deemed to have accepted and will be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

**11\. Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or how we use your Data please contact us by email at [**legal@babelgum.com**](mailto:legal@babelgum.com)

This Privacy Policy was last updated on 19th October 2010
